

EDUCATION

MAY 2018 - AUGUST 2018

Full Stack Code Immersion

Tech Talent South

Brief Description: Tech Talent South's Code Immersion programs is the perfect launching point for those who are passionate, persistent, and eager to learn.

AUGUST 2008 - MAY 2012

Bachelor in fine arts

University of South Carolina

Brief Description: My BFA in studio arts was focused on printmaking, photography, and graphic design.

SKILLS

HTML / CSS

Ruby on Rails

Javascript - Angular - React

Illustrator - Photoshop - InDesign

Sketch - Figma - Adobe XD

Professional Skills:

Web Design, Graphic Design, Wireframes, SEO, Branding, Program Management, Program Development

JIMMY HILLER

WEB DEVELOPER - UX DESIGNER

Phone: (803) 493-5237, | Email: hillerj l@gmail.com | Web: www.thejimmyhiller.com

ABOUT ME

I'm a dedicated, eager, passionate Web Designer with a goal to never stop learning. I have six years of valuable work experience from installing valuable art in museums, building national award winning programs for underprivileged students, and teaching a wide variety of visual and digital art. Teamwork, leadership, creativity, critical thinking, and problem solving are just a few of my biggest qualities.

EXPERIENCE

AUGUST 2018 - PRESENT

Freelance Web Design

Brief Description: After completing my cod immersion boot camp I went right to work advancing my skills and knowledge. With the mindset of establish a better understanding of Java-script and its popular platforms such as React and Angular

MAY 2018 - AUGUST 2010

Student (Full Stack Web Development)

Tech Talent South

Brief Description: My time at Tech Talent South was spent as a student gaining the fundamentals of full stack web development. I received general instruction on HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Ruby, Ruby on Rails, Git, API's, and Bootstrap

JANUARY 2016 - MAY 2018

Visual/Digital Art Teacher

Cardinal Newman School

Brief Description: My time at Cardinal Newman was spent developing curriculum and lesson plans for visual arts classes as well as graphic design classes.

AUG 2013 - JANUARY 2016

Community Programs Manager

Columbia Museum of Art

Brief Description: Provided many excellent, award winning and accessible opportunities for art education in South Carolina by taking art education lessons into the city, county and state to provide greater access and exposure to art to those who might not otherwise have the opportunity.

TECHNOLOGY

HTML - CSS - Javascript - Angular - React - Ruby on Rails - Bootstrap - Git - SEO Photoshop - Illustrator - Sketch - Figma - InDesign - MS Office - UX/UI Design